<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Atakan Yenel</title><link>https://atakanyenel.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Atakan Yenel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atakanyenel.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Practical Education in IoT through Collaborative Work on Open-Source Projects with Industry and Entrepreneurial Organizations</title><link>https://atakanyenel.github.io/publications/fie2018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atakanyenel.github.io/publications/fie2018/</guid><description>A talk about the responsive paper in FIE 2018 conference in San Jose, explains my experiences of learning cloud with a practical course in TUM. This paper is a joint effort to share our insights about this course and build a better path on teaching students cloud computing.</description></item><item><title>Kyma VSCode plugin</title><link>https://atakanyenel.github.io/projects/kyma-vscode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atakanyenel.github.io/projects/kyma-vscode/</guid><description>Kyma is an open source project designed for kubernetes that allows you to extend your cloud-based enterprise applications. This plugin connects your VS Code with the Kyma and allows you to monitor or deploy your resources directly from the editor.</description></item><item><title>Predictive Auto Scaling Application</title><link>https://atakanyenel.github.io/projects/passa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atakanyenel.github.io/projects/passa/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;PASSA (Predictive Auto Scaling Application) &amp;quot;is an open source tool for scaling cloud applications at specific datetimes. It checks the state of applications and VMs on the cloud and notifies any inconsistencies between the desired state and the current deployed state.&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://atakanyenel.github.io/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atakanyenel.github.io/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description></item><item><title>SSTK</title><link>https://atakanyenel.github.io/projects/sstk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atakanyenel.github.io/projects/sstk/</guid><description>This project deploys SSTK to Kubernetes. The project also includes developing a services architecture. Helm is used as deployment medium. Other infrastructures include Helm, GKE and GCP.</description></item></channel></rss>